♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组&@Daria拽妹黛薇儿
——·@严肃活泼小kk译制·——
把雪莉料酒藏起来不给老爸用吗?
Hiding the cooking sherry from Dad?
我要做面包 Daria
I'm going to make some bread, Daria.
这儿不是有超市么?
Isn't that what supermarkets are for?
Yeager一家人周末要过来呢
The Yeagers are coming for the weekend,
我不能用超市买的面包招待他们
and I can't serve them store-bought bread.
为啥?
Why not?
我有25年没见过他们了
I haven't seen them for twenty five years,
比方说他们会见到一个截然不同的Helen
and let's just say they know a different Helen.
一个做燕麦南瓜籽面包很拿手的Helen
A Helen famous for her oatmeal pumpkin seed loaf.
你把现在这个Helen怎么了?
And just what have you done with this Helen?
他们来啦
They're here!
希望他们不会觉得我有很大变化
I hope they don't think I've changed too much.
做你自己就好了
Just be yourself.
这是你一直贯彻给我的
That's what you've always told me.
我真懊悔说过那种蠢话
I could kick myself for that.
那是什么车?
What kind of car is that?
那不是车
That's not a car.
是时光机
It's a time machine.
Willow Coyote
Willow! Coyote!
哇 Helen
Wow, Helen!
- 亲 - 伙计
- Man! - My man!
你一点儿都没变
You haven't changed a bit.
你呀 瞧瞧你呀
And you! Well, just look at you!
哎呦 怎么Leary也一点都没变
Why, even Leary is exactly the same.
快过来 孩儿
Come here, boy!
还记得老Jake么?
Don't you remember old Jake?
等等 那肯定不是Leary
Wait, that can't be Leary.
它现在都快有30了吧
He'd be almost thirty by now!
这是Leary三世
This is Leary number three.
我们隔段时间就要替换原来那只
We had to replace the original a few times.
美国著名心理学家 作家 以其晚年对迷幻药的研究而知名
要是你能替换掉蒂莫西·利里就更好啦 对吧 亲?
If only you could do that with Timothy Leary, huh, man?
他们已经在着手了
They're working on it, man.
好吧 她俩可无可取代
Well, these two are irreplaceable.
我们的乖女 Quinn和Daria
Our girls, Quinn and Daria.
你的灵魂很苍老
You have a very old soul.
只是看起来比年龄成熟点
It just looks mature for its age.
这是什么复古行头 还是他们就这么打扮?
Is this a retro thing, or are they serious?
- 先把行李拿进去吧亲 - 我们轻装旅行
- Let's get your bags, man! - We travel light.
在脑子里
In the head.
在得到更多良好共鸣前 我得离开这儿
I gotta get out of here before I catch any more good vibes.
Daria 你不能把我扔在这儿和那些... 那些雅皮士在一起
Daria, you can't leave me here with those, those... yuppies!
雅皮士不颓废 不关心社会问题 只追求舒适和彰显自我性格
雅皮士是八十年代的产物
Yuppies are from the Eighties.
那应该怎么称呼...
So what do you call people
那些奇装异服又大肆谈论爱与和平的人?
with funny outfits who talk about peace and love and stuff?
星舰迷吧 不管怎样 我们中得有人留下来
Trekkies. Anyway, one of us should stay.
这是能进一步了解爸妈的难得机会
It's a rare opportunity to learn more about Mom and Dad.
为嘛我们会想那样做?
Why would we want to do that?
这样以后就能用来对付他们了
To use against them later.
挖到丑闻的话 给你20块
Twenty bucks if you dig up some dirt.
不好意思 我有约了
Sorry, I have a date.
你不干 我也不干
You're getting out of this, so am I.
Ethan 快来会会姑娘们
Ethan! Come meet the girls!
你说要给我20块吧?
You said twenty, right?
Zappa数位声道... Zappa模拟声道
appa digital... Zappa analog.
Zappa: 弗兰克·扎帕 美国六十年代摇滚乐先锋人物之一
我觉得听起来都差不多
Sounds the same to me.
那你还敢自称是音乐家?
And you call yourself a musician?
才没呢 我自称声音的翻译家
No, I call myself an interpreter of sound.
最高机密实验?
Top secret experiment?
我爸妈让我把他们的旧唱片拿去跳蚤市场卖了
My parents gave me their old records to sell at the flea market,
不过Trent说他想要
but now Trent wants to keep 'em.
这可是黑胶唱片情怀 亲
It's the warmth of vinyl, man.
跟你说 这是强烈的乐音
I'm telling you, it's a richer tone.
你调到收音机去了啦
You're tuned to the radio.
我还纳闷为什么Zapa要卖炸鱼柳
I wondered why Zappa was selling fish sticks.
跳蚤市场嘛? 要不要帮忙呀?
The flea market, huh? Need any help?
我们七点钟就得开摊了
We have to be there by 7:00 to set up.
没问题 Daria就是只早起的鸟儿
No problem. Daria's an early bird.
没什么事比看日出更好啦
There's nothing like watching the sun rise,
除了看太阳反向落下外
except watching the sun set in reverse.
接得好呀 Daria
Good one, Daria.
谢了哟
Mmm, umm, thanks.
好啦 这次让我们来反接插头
Okay, this time, let's reverse the polarity of the plug.
我来面西而立
And I'll stand facing west.
好哒
Ok cool.
你秀逗吗?
Are you nuts?
嘿 你随时都能回家 和雅皮士互换优格配方嘛
Hey, you could always go on home and swap yogurt recipes with the Yeagers.
我的优格怎么了?
And what's wrong with my yogurt recipe?
你得感谢我
You should thank me.
这可是你能和Trent共享宝贵时间的好机会
It's a chance for you to spend some quality time with Trent.
而且今年的跳蚤市场超浪漫的
And the flea market is so romantic this time of year.
听说草头娃娃们开得风华正茂
I hear the Chia Pets are in bloom.
好啦 就跳蚤市场了
All right, so, the flea market.
我们去定了
We're there.
好的 现在试试我站在铝箔上的效果
Okay, now let's try the thing where I stand on the aluminum foil.
过去的20年里 我们都通过邮寄 贩卖大麻做的吊床
So, for the past twelve years, we've been selling hammocks of hemp by mail.
由于大麻加工技术有了新进展
And with all the recent breakthroughs in hemp processing,
这会是最让人兴奋的一年啦
this could be our most exciting year yet!
噢 这可真有意思
Oh! That's fascinating.
Quinn 你今晚不是有约会么?
Quinn, didn't you have a date tonight?
我让Stacy替我去了
I got Stacy to fill in.
你喜欢运动是吧 小伙子?
You into sports, my man?
Ethan?
我们觉得这星球上的攻击性行为已经够多了
We think there's enough aggressive behavior on the planet
还不算上建立更多所谓的"良性竞争"
without creating more with quote unquote "healthy competition."
Ethan要是准备好了 就会去攀岩
Ethan's gonna rock climb, when he's ready.
没所谓 棒球也行
Whatever. Peas.
面包是不是用手发面的 一吃就知道
You can always tell when a bread isn't hand-kneaded.
人工揉的面团有更多的灵气
Hand-kneaded bread has more soul.
素食的东西我吃不饱
This veggie stuff never fills me up.
有人要来个汉堡么?
Anyone want a burger?
嘿 公平点嘛
Hey, fair's fair.
总有哪天 我们都会变成蠕虫的食物
We'll all be worm food someday.
Jake
Jake!
这是万物因果循环 Helen
It's the circle of life, Helen.
- 你知道吗亲 你有点咄咄逼人了- 我才没有
- You know, man, you've become kind of aggressive. - I have not!
- 都是吃荤的错 - 才不是
- It's the meat. - Is not!
你以前那种成熟又随性的态度怎么变了?
What ever happened to the mellow, let-it-be attitude you used to have?
Jake?
来吧 大家
Come on, everyone.
如果我们集中所有的正能量
If we focus all our positive energy,
我们就能让五角大楼从平地升起
we can make the Pentagon rise up off the ground.
1967反文化运动里雅皮士意用精神力来搬动五角大楼
升起来呀 擦
Rise, dammit!
愚蠢的五边形建筑
Stupid five-sided building.
还记得我们的小租房吗?
Remember our group house?
还不懂么?
Don't you see?
所谓有见识的男人都在压迫女人
So-called enlightened dudes are oppressing women,
就像社会平定动荡一样
just like society is putting down the movement.
我需要帮助 现在就要
I want some help, and I want it now!
哇 听起来妹子们好像在闹解放呢
Wow. Sounds like the girls are getting liberated.
真酷
Cool.
后来在大家散伙了以后
And then, after you guys split,
我们涂画包装了一辆公车 开进了沙漠
we painted a bus and drove out into the desert.
我真希望你能和我们在一起
I wish you would've stayed with us.
噢 Willow 做人要向前看
Oh, Willow. It was time for us to move on.
那只是你的看法
That's what you want to call it.
- 什么? - 亲爱的
- What? - Honey...
你什么意思嘛 Coyote?
What do you mean, Coyote?
没什么 我爱大家
Nothing, I love you guys.
只是我还记着你曾经的模样 仅此而已
It's just, I remember you as you were, that's all.
实际上我们还是老样子
We're still that way, deep down.
对呀 亲 我们还是老样子
Yeah, man! We're still that way!
什么样子?
What way?
摆脱肤浅的由利益主导的文化价值体系
Free of the shallow, superficial value system of a profit-driven culture
已经是大错特错了
gone terribly, terribly wrong.
当然啦 我们就是这种人嘛
Oh, sure, we're that way!
我能和老屋主夫人说话么?
May I speak to the old lady of the house?
Daria 你在哪呀?
Daria, where are you?
在Jane家 我能在她家过夜吗?
Jane's. Can I stay over?
我本来是想让你认识一下我们的朋友
I was hoping you would want to get to know our friends.
我苍老的灵魂已经在前世和他们相识了
My old soul has already made their acquaintance in a previous lifetime.
好吧 这样的话就能给Ethan腾出点空间了
Well, that does free up some space for Ethan.
他睡客房 我能让Willow和Coyote睡你的房间
He can take the guest room, and I can put Willow and Coyote in your room.
你要让他们睡我的房间?
You're going to put them in my room?
你最好把他们绑在床上以防他们漂走
You better tether them to the bed so they don't float away.
接下来《呕心小世界》恐怖故事:
A nightmare story of an enchanted kiss gone horribly wrong,
大错特错的魔力之吻
when Sick, Sad World returns.
搞定 我能在这睡了
Okay, I can stay.
你有什么能让我穿的睡衣么?
You have anything for me to sleep in?
甭谢我 谢奶奶
Don't thank me. Thank Grandma.
还有这呢 我们安置Daria的房间
And this, is where we keep Daria.
酷 告诉我爸妈我就睡这里
Cool. Tell Mom and Dad I'm sleeping here.
一旦你能把所有身外之物都塞进背包里
Once you could fit all your worldly possessions into a backpack.
一条牛仔裤 一些T恤 一本《偷走这本书》
Pair of jeans, a few T-shirts, a copy of Steal This Book.
书籍简介: 如何利用现存的体制谋生及电话偷窃术
作者Abbie Hoffman 著名反文化人士 "雅皮士"领导人
接下来 瞧瞧你自己
And now, look at you.
资本主义的拉拉队长 穿西装的叛徒 该死
A capitalist cheerleader, a sellout in a monkey suit! Dammit!
是时候翻身做主人了
It's time to take a stand!
明天绝不剃胡子
You're not gonna shave tomorrow.
拜托 Jakey 让别人也用用厕所嘛
Come on, Jakey, let someone else have a turn.
- Helen 你觉得"我的青春小鸟一去不回来"吗? - 当然不是啦
- Helen, do you think I'm past my prime? - Of course not.
你还是那么年轻有力
You're still quite the young buck.
怎么说呢 帅哥老了反而更帅
Anyway, good looking men get even handsomer as they mature.
哇 真可惜女人不是这样
Woo! Too bad it's not the same for women!
好多了 这下我啥都看不到
That's better. Now I can't see a thing.
明天可是个大日子
Big day tomorrow.
六点叫你起床 安安
We'll wake you at six. 'Night.
晚安
Good night!
安安 明早见
'Night, see you in the morning.
六点再过来
Come back at six.
已经六点啦
It is six.
那你怎么能这么精神?
Then how come you're so damn chipper?
熬夜可比早起简单多了
It was easier to stay up all night than to wake up early.
我们先去把东西搬上货车
We'll load the van.
货车?
Van?
你懂的 坦克
You know, the Tank.
太好喽
Oh, goody.
他们走了吗?
Are they gone?
别忘记带上钱
Don't forget some money.
嘿 奶奶不是有件同款睡袍吗?
Hey, doesn't Grandma have a nightgown like that?
我要把这个分到"自我放逐的装逼货"还是"怀才不遇"里?
Should I file this under "self-indulgent posers" or "underrated geniuses"?
问Trent或Jesse 随便问一个最早起床的人啦
Ask Trent or Jesse, whichever one wakes up first.
我猜之所以叫"跳蚤"市场 是因为它会让你想"逃走"
I guess they call it a flea market because it makes you want to flee.
好了啦 放轻松 我们今天会棒棒哒
Come on, relax. We're going to do well today.
我们的摊位有地理优势
We've got a choice location.
爱国者马桶盖套
我想买雪球
I'm looking for snow domes.
你们有卖的么?
You got any, girls?
抱歉 夫人
Sorry, ma'am.
我们只卖这些外星人留下来的奇怪圆盘唱片
All we have are these strange, flat discs the aliens left behind.
外星人你造吧?
You know about the aliens, don't you?
你很享受参与公众工作嘛?
You enjoy working with the public, don't you.
早上好
Morning!
向崭新的Jake问好
Say hello to a new Jake.
就是以前的那个Jake
The old Jake!
好久不见的Jake
The Jake you haven't seen for a while.
向饼干模具公司的Jake说再见
And goodbye to cookie-cutter corporate guy Jake.
cookie-cutter又为千篇一律 此处Jake说的是这个意思
那个Jake已经走啦 离开啦 不干啦
That Jake is gone, gone, gone.
你该不会是辞职了吧?
You didn't quit your job, did you?
没啦 我在留胡子呢
No, I'm growing a beard again.
那挺好的 亲爱的
Oh! That's great, dear.
嘿 Quinn 你觉得我的新造型咋样?
Hey, Quinn! How do you like my, new look?
老爸 你是在留山羊胡吗?
Dad, are you growing a goatee?
有够老土的
That's so two years ago.
对吧 Ethan?
Right, Ethan?
我觉得现在精力真集中
I really feel centered now.
- 胡子挺不错 - 谢谢
- Nice whiskers. - Thanks!
这儿有点挤了
Um, it's kind of getting crowded in here.
我还是和Ethan出去吃早餐吧
Why don't Ethan and I go out for breakfast.
你们就能好好坐一起追忆当年啦
You guys can sit around and remember things.
早餐? 我还以为要吃午餐了
Breakfast? I thought it was lunch time.
我回去睡觉了
I'm going back to bed.
你干嘛盯着我哥看?
Why are you staring at my brother?
无私的关心
Selfless concern.
我以为他嗝屁了
I think he stopped breathing.
他在休眠呢
Nah, he's entering a dormant stage.
大概十年后他就能破茧成蝶了
In about ten years he should emerge as a butterfly.
我猜你只能独守空房了
I guess you're gonna wait.
你们好呀 女士们
Hello, ladies!
我咋不知道你们也是主办人呢
I didn't know you were of an entrepreneur bent.
也许你们会友善地让我瞧瞧商品?
Perhaps you would be so kind as to show me your goods?
呕男 你在这干嘛?
Upchuck, what are you doing here?
我在找快餐奖赏的圣杯
I am on a quest for the Holy Grail of fast food premiums.
一个1985年加州产的仿真葡萄干橡胶套
A complete 1985 California Raisins posable eraser set.
要完好无损的才行
Only mint condition will do.
你的投资商么?
Your investors?
沉默搭档
Silent partners.
你们有没有《回头是岸》的原声带?
Do you by any chance have the cast recording of Somebody Up There Likes Me?
拳王Rocky Graziano的传记电影
没有 不过我们有《下面的人才不》
No, but we do have Somebody Down Here Doesn't.
我在想也许我能给你们一些销售建议
I wonder if I may provide you gals with a lesson in salesmanship.
你们将终身受益哟
It's a once in a lifetime offer.
两生受益怎么样?
How about once in two lifetimes.
好啦 现在就让这货告诉我们咋做
Now, now, let the boy show us how to do it.
我们就不用干了
Then we won't have to.
又回到我手上了
It's all coming back.
想试试吗 亲爱的?
You wanna try, honey?
真恶心 狗的口水 那只野兽
Ugh, dog drool. That beast!
出去
Outside!
你好? Eric?
Hello? Eric?
什么? 他们要把听证提前到这周?
What? They moved the hearing up to this week?
我20分钟内赶不过去呀
I can be there in 20 minutes.
说到紧张之处了啊
Talk about uptight.
放轻松
Mellow out, man.
没什么急事不能等到周一说
Nothing's so important that it can't wait till Monday,
你周末还在公司里关着自己干嘛呀?
what are you doing in the corporate cage on the weekend?
不去公园里散散步
Don't take a walk in the park.
这就对了 亲爱的
Right on, honey.
你还保留着优先权呀
You still have your priorities.
谁要接飞盘? 来呀 Leary
Who's up for frisbee? Come on, Leary!
Eric 就是啦 我当然是在讲笑
Eric? Yes, of course I was kidding.
瞧见了么 女士们
You see, ladies,
不用正确方法关闭交易
trying to close a sale without the proper technique
就像玩牌不用一整副牌
is like playing cards without a full deck.
你得把顾客当成上帝
You must treat your customers like a king.
这就是取胜的花招
This is the ace up your sleeves.
不这样做的话就是小丑牌 手里就只剩J了
You're a joker if you don't, and you'll be left with jack.
讲到两生受益的干货再叫醒我
Wake me when you get to the twos.
罗斯福?
FDR?
不 先生 我的马桶盖套上才没有什么社会主义者
No, sir, you won't find socialists on any of my toilet seats.
现在看哥亲身示范
Now, watch a pro in action.
嘿 DeMartino老师
Hey! Mr. DeMartino!
噢 Charles Ruttheimer
Well, Charles Ruttheimer.
什么事 Charles?
What is it, Charles?
作为栽培和育种的一员
As a man of culture and breeding,
我想您也许会对我们的部分听觉佳作感兴趣
I thought you might be interested in some of our audio gems.
你在尝试做可悲的奉承么 Ruttheimer先生?
Is this a pathetic attempt at flattery, Mr. Ruttheimer?
你精心蓄谋那么明显的烟雾弹
An obvious smoke screen for your calculated attempt
就是想把我从每周照看一群蠢货赚来的钱
at separate me from the payments I receive each week for babysitting
夺走吧?!
a bunch of determined idiots?!?!
我只是想向你推销些唱片....
I just wanted to sell you some records...
有没有Annette Funicello的?
Got anything by Annette Funicello?
首批米老鼠俱乐部成员之一
嘿 伙计 你修完这辆宝贝后
Hey, man, after you get this baby fixed up,
我们一起去俱乐部玩上几把咋样?
what do you say we go down to the club and play a round?
高尔夫球场就是生态灾难地
The golf course is an ecological disaster.
怎么 你不懂怎么挥杆吗?
What, you got trouble with your swing?
给 你们小子们也许想来点提神的
Here, we thought you boys might like some refreshments.
自制浆果汁
Home-bottled berry juice.
我们要去堆肥
We're going to start a compost pile.
一定很好玩吧?
Won't that be fun?
哇 这玩意真带劲
Wow! This is strong stuff!
放了天然的果胶
It's got natural pectins.
我爱果胶
I love pectins!
这就是最低价?
Is this the best you can do?
是的...
'Fraid so...
那好吧 我不买了
Well then, I guess I'm just going to have to walk away.
我要走咯....
I'm walking...
好呗 50美分
Okay, fifty cents.
谢谢亲
Thanks, man.
我的佣金呢?
What about my commission?
嘿 我们可是免费栽培你耶
Hey, we're training you for free.
好的 Trent 既然你回魂了
Well, Trent, now that you've returned to the land of the living,
也许你和Daria能去买点苏打
maybe you and Daria can go get us some soda.
要含咖啡因的?
With caffeine?
没问题 来呀?
No problem. Coming?
好
Sure.
慢慢来
Take your time!
我想吃点汉堡
I could use a burger.
我也去
I'll go with you.
呕霸 你能看会摊么?
Upchuck, can you handle the booth?
我什么都能搞定 小姐
I can handle much more than that, missy.
请问 那是《一瞥所见》的复刻版?
Excuse me! But is that a vintage copy of Eyefull?
1962年的
1962.
你哪里找到这么一个宝贝?
Where did you find such a treasure?
那边的摊位
That booth over there.
没事 我来付
That's okay, I got it.
- 欠你啦 - 下次还
- I owe you one, then. - Next time.
所以 Janey说你这周都在躲你爸妈的朋友?
So, Janey says you're avoiding your parent's friends this weekend.
他们阳光活力的60年代乐观主义
Their sunny Sixties optimism
快要抵消掉我90年代的玩世不恭了
tends to cancel out my bitter Nineties cynicism.
赖死不走的嬉皮士?
Holdover hippies?
嗯 他们是"一切从简"的狂热崇拜者
Yeah. They're big believers in the concept of voluntary simplicity.
我也得用上那词
I gotta use that.
比"一贫如洗"好听多了
Sounds much better than broke.
我猜你得给他们点权利
I guess you gotta give them some credit.
民事权利 环境保护 妇女运动
Civil rights, environmentalism, the women's movement.
给他们点那个年代人们信赖的东西
People believed in stuff back then.
我知道
I know.
那有什么不对?
What's up with that?
我知道你在想什么 不过我可是顶天立地的牛人了
I know what you're thinking, but I've turned into the man!
我从来没称过你牛人 亲
I'd never call you the man, man.
人 也许有 可不牛
Man, maybe, but not the man.
我讨厌这傻缺的生锈废物
I hate this stupid rusty piece of junk!
而且我厌倦了买散装食品
And I'm tired of buying food in bulk!
每次上完厕所都不能冲 因为会浪费水资源
And not flushing every time I go because it wastes water!
我还年轻 我的信仰都怎么了?
I'm still young. What happened to my beliefs?
做能解决问题的人 不做制造麻烦的人 又怎么了?
What happened to being part of the solution, not part of the problem?
我恨死揉面团了
I hate kneading bread.
嗯?
What?
我... 恨死... 揉... 面团啦
I... hate... kneading... bread!
该死
Damn!
噢 Willow 来
Oh Willow! Here!
亲 你能教我打高尔夫么?
Man, can you teach me how to play golf?
当然可以 亲
Of course I can, man.
我们能坐着这小推车转悠转悠么?
And can we ride around on those little carts?
没问题 伙计
Sure thing, pal!
嘿 有机化肥的蒸气浴嘛? 真酷耶
Hey, some kind of organic nutrient steam bath, right? Cool!
Jake 我们在垃圾堆里摔倒啦 感觉自己就像猪
Jake, we fell on our asses in a pile of garbage. I feel like a hog.
猪 我想死培根了
Hog! I miss bacon.
噢 谢谢你如此的关心
Oh, thanks so much for your concern!
哇 妹子们好像在闹革命哟
Wow, sounds like the girls are getting liberated.
酷
Cool.
老爸 浆果汁又发酵了
Dad, the berry juice fermented again.
小心点
You gotta watch that.
走吧 我给你买个泥浆杯
Come on, I'll buy you a slush cup.
真是时候
It's about time!
身上有钱没?
Got any money?
我的剃须刀呢?
Where's my razor?
你瞧 在我看来
You see, my theory is
原始的狩猎本能在现代社会可没有出路
that our primitive hunting instinct has no outlet in modern society.
酷
Cool.
所以说 与其说跟踪动物
So, rather than stalking animals,
倒不如说是购物和寻找猎物
we substitute the shopping experience, and hunt for objects.
酷
Cool.
然后呢 Jesse 当我们睡着
And then, Jesse, while we're asleep,
猎物就会醒来策划阴谋 要侵略我们的文明
the objects come to life and plot their secret take over our civilization.
2007年4月1号 就是他们暴动的日子
April 1st, 2007. That's the day they make their move!
酷
Cool.
我不知道
I don't know.
这些人都在交换着没用的垃圾
All these people swapping useless junk.
Yeager一家人也许掌握了些情况
Maybe the Yeagers are onto something.
至少他们没有陷入无止尽的消费里
At least they're not caught up in a constant state of consumer frenzy.
我猜如果你还是要执着一些六十年代的事物
Yeah, I guess if you're gonna insist on holding on to something from the Sixties,
爱与和平可比午餐盒好多了
peace and love beats a Get Smart lunchbox.
特别是里面还放着午餐的话
Especially if the lunch is still in it.
走吧 去替Jesse和Jane的班吧
Well, let's go give Jesse and Jane a break.
太晚了
Too late.
谁在看摊呀?
Who's watching the booth?
呕男
Upchuck.
不是吧
I don't think so.
看这 Demartino老师
Here, Mr. Demartino!
我找到另一期的《单身汉机密》
I found another issue of Bachelor Confidential!
你弥补了过错 Charles
You have redeemed yourself, Charles.
至少不用搬那么多货回去啦?
Less to carry home?
我们还剩三张Boston乐队的唱片
Well, we do have three copies left to "Boston."
至少我们不是贪钱的资本主义猪 对吧 Daria?
At least we're not money grabbing capitalist pigs, right, Daria?
嗯 我们只是一切从简的中坚分子
Yeah, we're just hard core believers in voluntary simplicity.
不 警察从没正式起诉过他们
No, they never formally charged them,
不过第二天就把他们关大牢里去了
they did keep them there in jail for the next day.
嘿 我的眉笔哪去了?
Hey, where's my eyebrow pencil?
这猛料至少也得值20块钱
This has gotta be worth at least twenty bucks.
好的 再说一遍我妈是怎么揍警察的?
Now, tell me again about how Mom punched out the cop.
你确定你不要了吗?
You're sure you don't want this?
我从来没用过呢
I never use it.
这能大大缩短我给Ethan和Coyote烘焙的时间
This will cut way down on the time I spending baking for Ethan and Coyote.
大姐 瞧瞧冷冻的贝果
Sister, meet the frozen bagel.
又称百吉饼 传统的犹太面包圈
嘿 亲们 天快黑啦
Hey, guys, it's getting dark.
你们什么时候进屋呀?
When are you going to come in?
就快啦
In a minute.
我在教Coyote怎么避免打出曲线球
I'm just showing Coyote how to drive without slicing!
有进步
Better!
姑娘们 我期望你还吃得下饭
Girls, I expected you for dinner.
在我正式下令关你们禁闭前 要不要解释一下你们的行踪?
Before I officially ground you, would you care to account for your whereabouts?
好的 不过首先 提点问题
Sure. But first, a few questions.
问题一
Number one:
69年8月 你怎么会在Boulder市监狱呆了一晚?
why did you spend a night in jail in Boulder in August, 1969?
谢谢你的营销策划
Thanks for that marketing plan, man.
我们要去给彩虹吊床公司的懦夫们好看
We're going to kick the butts of those wimps over at Rainbow Hammocks.
嘿 别留活口 大哥
Hey, take no prisoners, man.
掠夺是天性
Predatory behavior is all natural.
Ethan?
嗯?
Yeah?
你都没说过人家很可爱嘛?
You never told me whether you thought I was, you know, cute?
噢 当然 你很可爱
Oh, well, sure, you're cute.
谢谢
Thanks.
是很... 你懂的... 在肤浅的层面...
In a, you know, shallow, superficial way.
谢谢
Thanks.
要想不夸你 很难吧?
It's very hard not to compliment you, isn't it?
Daria 你用不着这么说啦
Oh, Daria, you don't have to say that.
Daria 你觉得异地恋是不是挺好的?
Daria, do you think long-distance relationships are a good idea?
嗯 为何我俩不试试?
Yeah. Why don't you and I try one?
你们懂的 孩子们 沉湎过去根本没有意义
You know, kids, it's pointless to try to go back in time.
你得活在当下 这就是老爸我现在要做的
You have to live in the present, and I'm going to start right now.
第一步就是 扔掉我的所有黑胶唱片
First things first: I'm getting rid of all my vinyl records.
嘿 Daria 你想要唱片吗?
Hey, Daria! You want 'em?
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组